Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Marketing Files, 1994-2015; 10
  - Lee Willoughby-Harris, 11.3
    - Alexander- Postcard, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Cvetkovich- An Archive of Feelings, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Hill- Something All Our Own, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Wesley- Postcard- Hit Me, Fred, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Hornstein- Postcard, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Ringgold- Postcard, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Rosenberg/ Harding, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Ridgeway- Postcard- It's All For Sale, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Edelman- Postcard, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Sommer- Postcard, 2004 (Box 43)
    - D. Thomas- Postcard, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Hunt- Postcard REPRINT, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Devins- au flyer, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Perry- Fall '04 au flier, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Wallace (for author), 2004 (Box 43)
    - Clarke, K.M., 2004 (Box 43)
    - Goldstein- The Spectacular City, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Greenough/ Tsing, 2003 (Box 43)
    - Weinbaum- Wayward Reproductions, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Roth- The Encylopedia of Duke Basketball, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Harlow and Carter, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Lawrence- Postcard, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Frankenberg- Postcard, 2004 (Box 43)
    - Gonzales- Day: Lynching in the West, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Weiss/ Steve Lacy, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Kosek- Understories, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Davidson, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Vaughan/ Lewis, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Sale Postcard- After Eden, 2006-2007 (Box 44)
    - List Research, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Data Bases, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Libraries- Mailing List Information, 1997-2001 (Box 44)
    - Lowry- Demensions of Federalism, 2003 (Box 44)
    - Talarico Prize Information, 1995 (Box 44)
    - Book Reviews, 1991 (Box 44)
    - Gavins, Raymond- Reviews, 1977-1987 (Box 44)
    - Standford Bio, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Environmental Media, 1992-1997 (Box 44)
    - National Audubon Society, 1991-1995 (Box 44)
    - AUPG Direct Mail Projects, 1995-1997 (Box 44)
    - Jayne- Negative Poetics (Box 44)
    - Silk Calvin Hoover Bio, 1985-1988 (Box 44)
    - Social Medicine Reader, 1996-1997 (Box 44)
    - Comp. Reading Copies, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Samples Copies to Deans, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Henderson Response Report, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
    - Halberstam, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Hauerwas Reader, 2001 (Box 44)
    - Conf. Flier Huggins, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Lipkin- author brochure, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Ludwikowski, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Metzl e-campaigns, 2003 (Box 44)
    - Rich/ Chick Flicks au brochure, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Rony au brochure, 1996 (Box 44)
    - Vaughan, 1996 (Box 44)
    - Whitehead au brochure, 2002 (Box 44)
    - Yamazaki au brochure, 1995 (Box 44)
    - Art Song CD Set, 1997-1998 (Box 44)
    - Brumfield- author flyer, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Brander-Rasmussen e-campaign, 2001 (Box 44)
    - S. Cohen- author brochure, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Coombe- author brochure, 1999 (Box 44)
    - Corredor/ Lukacs After Communism, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Curtis- Free Speech- au brochure, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Davidson/ Hatcher, 2002 (Box 44)
    - Ewing/ Arguing Sainthood, 1997 (Box 44)
    - Fujitani, et al, 2001 (Box 44)
    - Next Wave Series Flyer, 2001 (Box 44)
    - Hill- Something All Our Own, 2003 (Box 44)
    - Jacquard, 2002 (Box 44)
    - Move to Brightleaf, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Staff Party, 1992 (Box 44)
    - Speakers Series, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Back to Back/ Duke Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - DTW Invitation, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Perkins Exhibit, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Vaughan- Advertising Information, 1996 (Box 44)
    - Blackwell-Subject Mailers, 1994 (Box 44)
    - Moss Spec. Marketing, 1995-1996 (Box 44)
- Steve Cohn papers, 1925-2019; 11
  Series contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - The Ashbel Brice Years, 1925-1988 (Box 381)
  - Founding of Duke University Press and Trinity College Press, 1926-1987 (Box 381)
  - Journals of Personality, 1945-1997 (Box 381)
  - Job Change (BW to Journals Manager), 1981-1983 (Box 381)
  - EAB Origins, 1982-1986 (Box 381)
  - SAC as Journals Manager to Associate Director for Journals, 1984-1993 (Box 381)
  - The Rowson Years (DUP 5 Year Plan-Draft), 1986-1991 (Box 381)
  - NCSC, 1989-1991 (Box 381)
  - IMRN, 1990-2001 (Box 381)
  - IMRN Sale and History, 1990-2001 (Box 381)
  - Change of Leadership, 1993-1994 (Box 381)
  - Transition to Director of Publishing Operations, 1993-1995 (Box 381)
  - SAC as Director of Pub. Ops., 1993-1998 (Box 381)
  - Sales of Journals of Personality Rationale and Use of Funds (IMRN), 1997 (Box 381)
  - Steve Cohn Becomes Director, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Whole Press Staff Messages, 1998-2004 (Box 381)
  - Message to the Duke University Press Staff, 2002-2018 (Box 381)
  - SAC Contract Review, 2003 (Box 381)
  - Whole Press Staff Messages, 2005-2009 (Box 381)
  - Duke Scholarly Collection for Books Presentation, 2007 (Box 381)
  - Review, 2009 (Box 381)
  - Whole Press Staff Messages, 2010-2015 (Box 381)
  - Review of Reappointment, 2014 (Box 381)
  - Reorganization, 2015 (Box 381)
  - Whole Press Staff Messages, 2016 (Box 381)
  - Author's Note, 2019 (Box 381)
  - Duke Press External Review, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Duke Press External Review Resolution, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Response of Duke University Press to the Report of the 1998 External Review Team (Box 381)
  - Draft Response of Duke University Press to the Report of the 1998 External Review Team (Box 381)
  - Review of the Report Team, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Editorial Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Production Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Marketing Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Journals Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Central Admin. Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 381)
  - Progress on the 199-1999 Five-Year Plan: Duke University Self-Assessment 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Business Office Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Editorial Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Production Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Marketing Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Journals Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Central Admin. Department Self-Assessment for External Review Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Review of the Report Team 2, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Executive Summary, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Introduction, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Mission, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Goals of Duke University Press, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Changing Environment for University Press Publishing: Obstacles and Opportunities, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Desired Outcomes, Strategies for Development, Benchmarks for Success, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Five-Year Plan Draft: Envisioned Staff Additions, 2000 (Box 382)
  - Duke University Press- A Rationale and Plan- Executive Summary, 1994-1999 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan: Introduction, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan: Mission, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan: Goals for Duke University Press, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan: Desired Outcomes, Strategies for Development, Benchmarks for Success, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan: Appendix, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Financial Trends Report, 2017 (Box 382)
  - DUP Self-Assessment, 1998 (Box 382)
  - Marketing Plans and Projections, 1997-1998 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Executive Summary with Steve Cohn's Notes, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan (Copy), 1994 (Box 382)
  - Administration Responses to 1994 DUP Plan (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Projections, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Background Material (including Cited Material), 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Financial Projections: Meetings with Jim and Mike plus Materials, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Submission/Response: Five Year Plan, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Midlist Books, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Suggestions from Press Managers, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Staff Responses to Planning/Priorities Questionnaire, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Drafts of Editorial Planning Document, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Pieces of 1994 Five Year Plan (Originals?) (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan Support Docs, 1999 (Box 382)
  - Stanley Fish (Articles and Correspondence with Admin), 1993 (Box 382)
  - Press Review Committee 9/93 (George Wright and Roberts, Cox, Spicer, Cohn), 1993 (Box 382)
  - Duke Press Operations Analysis: Joe Mazzola's Class, 1994 (Box 382)
  - Financial Task Force, 1993 (Box 382)
  - Crisis Documents, 1993 (Box 382)
  - 5/92 Press Review by Outside Review Team, 1993 (Box 382)
  - Five Year Plan, 1992 (Box 383)
  - Reviewing/Planning Documents, 1992 (Box 383)
  - Planning: Various, 1992-1994 (Box 383)
  - Books Planning Documents, 1993 (Box 383)
  - Early Years, 1926-1951 (Box 383)
  - The Ashbel Brice Years, 1958-1965 (Box 383)
  - Plan, 2010 (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan, 2010; 2 folders (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan 2010: Drafts (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan, 2000; 2 folders (Box 383)
  - Review Team Appendixes, 2010 (Box 383)
  - January 2006 Planning Retreat (Box 383)
  - Summary of 2003 Aborted Planning Process, 2003-2005 (Box 383)
  - 2003 Planning Process: Key Documents (Box 383)
  - Planning '03: Stuff from Managers Meeting Folder, 2003 (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan Process '03: Stuff from Books Managers' and Books Review Group Folders, 2003 (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan Projections, 2002 (Box 383)
  - Managers' Comments on Five Year Plan Draft, 1999 (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan: Meetings, Conversations, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 383)
  - Past Planning Documents to Peter/John/Jan, 1998-1999 (Box 383)
  - Material for 1998 Review Team: Dean's Council (Box 383)
  - Press Response to 1998 Review Team Report (Box 383)
  - Review Team Report: Academic Priorities Committee (APC) and Duke Administration, 1998 (Box 383)
  - Review Team Report, 1998 (Box 383)
  - Post-Visit Correspondence with 1998 Review Team (Box 383)
  - Correspondence with Leigh DeNeef and Review Team re: 1998 Review (Box 383)
  - Self-Assessment for Review Team, 1998 (Box 383)
  - 1998 Review Team: Preliminaries and Procedures (Box 383)
  - Five Year Plan Progress Report, 1998 (Box 383)
  - Official Press Matters, 1953-1967 (Box 383)
  - Annual Reports: Editorial, 1942-52 (Box 384)
  - John Menapace Festschrift, 1984 (Box 384)
  - Reports on the Activities of Duke University Press, 1947-1952 (Box 384)
  - Performance Planning and Review: Self-Assessment for Provost, 2000-2018 (Box 384)
  - Review Team Report, 1992 (Box 384)
  - Review Team: Report, response, and other materials, 2010 (Box 384)
  - Draft of aborted 2000 plan and related materials (Box 384)
  - Plan and responses aftermath, 1992 (Box 384)
  - Review and team responses, 1998 (Box 384)
  - Association of American University Presses (AAUP), 1999-2017; 83 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word, PDF, MS Excel, and RTF formats).
    Administrative records restricted until 2042.
  - AAUP compensation survey, 2012; 1 file; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0002)
    Includes a document file (MS Excel format).
    Personnel records restricted until 2087.
  - Budget cover letters, 2000-2019; 20 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word format).
    Administrative records restricted until 2014.
  - Budget organization charts, 2016-2018; 2 files; less than 1 megabyte (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0002)
    Includes document files (PDF format).
    Personnel records restricted until 2093.
  - Charlotte Initiative, Licensing Principles Research Team, 2015-2018; 30 files; approximately 5 megabytes (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word, PDF, and MS Excel formats).
    Administrative records restricted until 2043.
  - Duke Scholarly Exhibits Board Meetings, 2015-2018; 44 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word, MS Excel, and PDF formats).
  - Duke Scholarly Exhibits Financial documents, 2000-2018; 12 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Excel and MS Word formats).
  - Duke Scholarly Exhibits Governance, 1999-2019; 6 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Administrative records restricted until 2044.
  - Duke Scholarly Exhibits Reports, 2001-2015; 16 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - DUP Digital Strategy, 2014-2015; 4 files; approximately 6 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Administrative records restricted until 2040.
  - Editorial Advisory Board, 1999-2019; 75 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - History of DUP, 2019; 2 files; less than 1 megabyte (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - Letters, memoes, and agendas, 1999-2018; 91 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - Multi-year and strategic planning, 1998-2019; 148 files; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - DUP Policies, 2010-2019; 18 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word and PDF formats).
  - Proposals and contracts, 1999-2019; 123 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
  - Talks and papers, 2001-2018; 130 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word, PDF, and MS PowerPoint formats).
- Executive Support Shared email, 2001-2019
  Email messages transferred from the University Press's Executive Support shared email inbox, particularly those identified by Steve Cohn. Messages were created and stored in Microsoft Outlook PST format, with a MBOX derivative created.
  - AUP_SPP email messages, 2007-2016; 1204 messages; approximately 150 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
    Original messages in PST mailbox format, with derivatives generated in MBOX mailbox format.
    Personnel records restricted until 2091.
  - Books email messages, 2001-2016; 3745 messages; approximately 315 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
  - Library email messages, 2003-2016; 364 messages; approximately 17 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
  - Academic Pub email messages, 2012-2015; 31 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
    Personnel records restricted until 2090.
  - Days in Residence email messages, 2015-2019; 115 messages; approximately 21 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
    Personnel records restricted until 2094.
  - 2009 DUP Annual Meeting email messages, 790 messages; approximately 44 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
    Personnel records restricted until 2084.
  - Open-Access email messages, 2010-2016; 5071 messages; approximately 553 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
  - Policies email messages, 2008-2016; 118 messages; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
  - Provost-and-President-Offices email messages, 2001-2016; 421 messages; approximately 33 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0003)
  - BEdit email messages, 2018-2019; 230 messages; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - DUPConnect email messages, 2018-2019; 7 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - EAB2 email messages, 2019; 28 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Finances - Trends and Analyses email messages, 2018; 77 messages; approximately 9 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Instructions email messages, 2018-2019; 1 message; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Journals email messages, 2015-2016; 26 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2041.
  - Africa UP email messages, 2012-2014; 30 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2039.
  - Books about Duke email messages, 2015-2016; 2 messages; approximately 0 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Brodhead book email messages, 2016-2017; 77 messages; approximately 6 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Capitalization email messages, 2015; 5 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Center for Creative Leadership email messages, 2009-2018; 69 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Charlotte Initiative email messages, 2015-2018; 1176 messages; approximately 124 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Directors Meeting 2012 email messages, 2011-2012; 162 messages; approximately 6 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2037.
  - Duke Today Spotlight email messages, 2018; 31 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Durham County Book email messages, 2010-2011; 45 messages; approximately 8 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2036.
  - Esposito Mellon Survey email messages, 2014-2017; 19 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - FHI Faculty Book Celebration email messages, 2016; 33 messages; approximately 4 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Internal Audit Report 2011 email messages, 2011-2012; 22 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Logo email messages, 2016; 16 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Media Insurance email messages, 2012-2014; 15 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Miller-Young email messages, 2014; 3 messages; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Multistaker email messages, 2015-2017; 322 messages; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Open Access Addenda email messages, 2008-2013; 107 messages; approximately 6 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2038.
  - Ralph Snyderman email messages, 2011-2016; 13 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Reorg email messages, 2015-2016; 120 messages; approximately 8 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Rice-Duke Collaboration email messages, 2011-2012; 18 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Roses for the Soul email messages, 2016; 1 message; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - TRLN email messages, 2011-2015; 47 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Work Culture email messages., 2007; 10 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2032.
  - 2008 Annual Meeting email messages, 56 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
    Administrative records restricted until 2033.
  - Academic Programs Committee email messages, 2011; 30 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Planning email messages, 2006-2016; 1044 messages; approximately 94 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Reports email messages, 2013-2016; 170 messages; approximately 250 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)
  - Univ-Assessment email messages, 2009-2016; 141 messages; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA07080002-SET-0004)